Fred's gotta go... to Camp Iwannapeepee!
FRED 3: Camp Fred is a family, tv movie, comedy film directed by Jonathan Judge.
Schools out, and Fred Figglehorn's dream of water slides, horseback riding and monkey butlers during the summer
turns into a nightmare of gruel and poisonous berries when his mom signs him up to an unsanitary camp.
Fred Figglehorn, played by Lucas Cruikshank.
Kevin, played by Jake Weary.
Fred's Mom, played by Siobhan Fallon Hogan.
Diesel, played by Carlos Knight.
Bertha, played by Daniella Monet.
Magoo, played by Joey Bragg.
Fred 3: Camp Fred is a 2012 American comedy film directed by Jonathan Judge.
It is the third and final installment in the Fred trilogy,
following Fred 2: Night of the Living Fred.
Released on July 28, 2012, the film stars Lucas
Cruikshank, Tom Arnold, Jake Weary, and John Cena.
The film received mixed reviews.
The tone is lighthearted.